<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshops on Melisa Retreat</title>
    <link>https://melisa.org.pl/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshops on Melisa Retreat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 19:34:17 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://melisa.org.pl/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://melisa.org.pl/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 16:47:50 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://melisa.org.pl/en/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;isabella&#34;&gt;Isabella&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started practicing Yoga with age 19 and through my regular practice I came in touch with meditation also. Different teachers and influences accompanied my path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pranayoga.at/&#34;&gt;My first yoga studio&lt;/a&gt; I visited in Vienna and I can still highly recommend it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adelheid Ohlig who created &lt;a href=&#34;https://luna-yogaweg.at/&#34;&gt;Luna Yoga&lt;/a&gt;. Here I discovered the power of Yoga in the female form. I learnt a lot with Gyöngyi in Vienna.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Ireland I completed my teacher training in 2017 and since then I teach on a regular basis. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ardnahoo.com/&#34;&gt;Noeleen Tyrrell&lt;/a&gt; offereda new energetic way with Anusara Yoga.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The gentle side of body movement I experienced with Somatic Yoga and &lt;a href=&#34;https://lisapetersen.yoga/&#34;&gt;Lisa Petersen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;www.jampaling.org&#34;&gt;Jampa Ling&lt;/a&gt;, the Tibetan Buddhist center in Ireland, I have practiced meditation and studied buddhism for years. Also, I have worked as a housekeeper and yoga teacher in the center.
If you like to support the center in any way, you can &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jampaling.org/about-us/support-jampa-ling/&#34;&gt;donate here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another project I treasure and volunteered for is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.projekt-ruanda-erika-hronicek.at/&#34;&gt;Projekt Ruanda&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;raphael&#34;&gt;Raphael&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Ireland I had the idea of opening a retreat center in Poland. Now we are here to make it happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve learned Kum Nye Yoga in Dzogchen Beara, and I’ve deepened my meditation practice in Jampa Ling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;future-plans&#34;&gt;Future Plans&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;d like to invite people with special skills like healers, high sensitive beings and all these, who are overwhelmed by the modern world and create a retreat area. We would like to offer a solution for the individual seeker of peace in a small setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yurts, simple but comfortable furnished, give the choice to live short or long term in a small community. It is possible to meditate, eat and work together. Also, it is important to experience relaxation and find stillness in us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The solitary yurts can provide self-catering options. There are different ways of cultivating a solitary retreat, and we can help to organize a daily routine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
